export const mentorSkills = [
  { id: 1, skills: "technology" },
  { id: 2, skills: "domain" },
  { id: 3, skills: "business-skills" },
];

export const mentorshipAreas = [
  { id: 1, area: " All" },
  { id: 2, area: "Trouble Shooting" },
  { id: 3, area: "Career Guidance" },
  { id: 4, area: "Development Problems" },
];

export const mentorAvailabilityTimings = [
  { id: 1, timings: "weekdays" },
  { id: 2, timings: "weekends" },
  { id: 3, timings: "saturday" },
  { id: 4, timings: "sunday" },
];
export const mentorFaqData = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "What forms of payment can I use?",
    answer: "You can pay by credit or debit card  or upi to make transaction.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What are the costs for paying online?",
    answer:
      "There are no signup costs or subscription fees. There are fees imposed by IPractiwiz for returned/cancelled payments, and your bank may charge you a fee based on the bank’s fee schedule.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "How should I enter my credit card information?",
    answer:
      "The information you enter on the Payment screen must be exactly the same as it appears on your credit card. This information collected will be used to authorize your payment.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "How will I know that my payment has been accepted?",
    answer:
      "After you submit your payment, you will see a payment confirmation screen. It will contain your payment confirmation message. You will also receive a confirmation email after your transaction is submitted. The email will include your booking appointment confirmation message.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "How long does it take for a credit card transaction to process if I pay online?",
    answer:
      "Credit card transactions typically take 48 hours to settle. An authorization is issued immediately; however, it takes 48 hours for the money to be moved.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Do I need to notify my bank or change bank accounts?",
    answer:
      "No, your current bank account (checking or savings) will work fine. So many payments are made electronically now that banks are already prepared for online payments.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What information do I need to make a payment?",
    answer:
      "The only information you need to have available to complete a payment transaction is your email address, password and your bank account or credit card information.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Can I use a credit card to pay my bill(s)?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you can. There is NO convenience fee when using credit cards.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Can I use a debit card to pay my bill(s)?",
    answer:
      "Yes, although technically your debit card will be processed like a credit card and you will not be asked to enter a pin number.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Will I have online access to my account?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you will have 24/7 access to your account for invoice review and payment, payment history and customer service requests",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Who do I contact with questions about a bill?",
    answer:
      "If you are unable to find the information you need in your online payment history or open invoices, please call the Practiwiz between 8 a.m. and 5 p.m..",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "What if this website is down or for some reason I am unable to use this site?",
    answer:
      "Please be aware that finance charges (for Commercial Accounts Only) will not be waived if this website is inoperable for any reason or if data entry errors occur. If the website is inoperable, please call the Practiwiz.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "If I have additional questions or I am having trouble registering, who should I call?",
    answer:
      "The Milford Water Department can answer most questions at 12345678 between 8:00 a.m. and 5:00 p.m., but if the website is down or inoperable, please call.",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "Is my information secure?",
    answer:
      "Practiwiz uses the highest standards in Internet security. Any information retained is not shared with third parties.",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question:
      "Is my credit card and checking account information safe when I pay online?",
    answer:
      "Absolutely. Invoice Cloud will safely store all of your financial information using Payment Card Industry (PCI) Compliant systems. This includes truncating (abbreviating) account numbers so that even your biller does not see your complete account information.",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "Who has access to my account?",
    answer:
      "You and the Practiwiz's authorized staff. No one will have access to your financial information as all check routing numbers and credit card numbers are truncated, so you never have to worry about security. As a security precaution, we don’t even show your full financial information back to you.",
  },
];
